‎目标在移动 ‎我在密切监视目标
I have eyes on target.
‎联邦调查局 ‎在24小时监视菲尔布朗顿
The FBI has Phil Brunton under 24-hour surveillance.
‎莫斯的首席战略家 ‎怎么会和生物恐怖威胁有关
How is Moss' chief strategist connected to the bioterror threat?
‎联邦调查局发现布朗顿曾邀请某人
Feds found someone solicited by Brunton
‎研发针对特定生物种族的传染病
to research and develop bioethnically targeted infections.
‎已经确认了
We've confirmed that?
‎国家安全局已介入 他们发现
NSA was brought in, and they've now tied Brunton
‎布朗顿和死去的恐怖分子蒙伯格 ‎有通话往来记录
to the dead terrorist, Momberg, through phone records.
‎我要小心绕过这个 ‎大家都知道的大老党问题吗
Do I have to tiptoe around the GOP elephant in the room?
‎莫斯是否参与其中
Is Moss involved?
‎-联邦调查局不知道 ‎-他不可能参与
-FBI doesn't know. -He couldn't be.
‎如果参与了 ‎他忠诚而狡猾的同党也永远不会说
Well, if he is, his loyal attack weasel will never tell.
‎莫斯在民调中领先
Moss is ahead in the polls.
‎布朗顿会保持沉默 ‎希望在他胜利后获得原谅
Brunton will stay quiet, hoping for a pardon if he wins.
‎逮捕的事情怎样了
Where are we at with the arrest?
‎这个问题让司法部很多人 ‎都避之不及 称病躲避
That is the question causing a run on Imodium at the DOJ.
‎大陪审团下发了一份密封起诉书
The grand jury handed down a sealed indictment,
‎但瓦格斯局长向来以 ‎保证联邦调查局不参与政治为荣
but Director Vargas prides himself on keeping the FBI apolitical.
‎所以他们把这事 ‎秘密传回白宫顾问办公室
Which is why they back-channeled this through the White House Counsel's office.
‎联邦调查局长期以来都坚持
The bureau has a long-standing protocol
‎避免在选举前几周
of refraining from making major decisions in investigations
‎-做出重大调查决定的惯例 ‎-只剩不到一周了
-in the weeks preceding an election. -We're less than a week out.
‎现在逮捕看起来像是
An arrest now gives the appearance
‎他们在利用自己的权力影响选举结果
that they're using their authority to influence the outcome.
‎我们不知道放任布朗顿逍遥法外 ‎他会做出什么事
We don't know what Brunton could do if he's allowed to remain free.
‎对不起 现在我必须介入 ‎我的职责是保护美国人民
I'm sorry, but I have to step in here. My job is to protect the American people.
‎我的职责是保护你
And my job is to protect you.
‎作为总统 你无权下令起诉
As president, you do not have authority to order a prosecution.
‎滥用职权会为你带来一系列后果
Abuse of power opens you to a range of consequences.
‎想想媒体
And think of the optics.
‎下令逮捕你政治对手的高级代理人
Ordering the arrest of your political rival's top surrogate?
‎我还是要做些什么
I still have to do something.
‎你的干预会危害到案件的进展
Your interference could jeopardize the case.
‎我强烈建议你不要插手
I strongly advise you stay out of it.
‎好吧 谢谢你 罗谢尔 谢谢
Okay, fine. Thank you, Rachelle. Thank you.
‎关于媒体 她说得对
She's right about the optics.
‎你在民调中落后 ‎这样做看起来很有政治意味
You're behind in the polls. It'll look political.
‎你认识瓦格斯
You know Vargas.
第三季   第九集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
精校
发行
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
‎你是替总统带话
You're speaking on behalf of the president?
‎他想让你知道 这届政府
He wants you to know that this isn't a White House
‎不会试图干预调查
that's going to interfere in an investigation.
‎那我们为什么 ‎要在安全摄像头盲区会面 马斯
Then why are we meeting in a security camera blind spot, Mars?
‎瓦格斯 联邦调查局应该按章办事
Vargas, the FBI should proceed by the book.
‎我们确实在按章办事
We are.
‎我们不掺和选举
We don't put our thumb on the electoral scale.
‎我的意思是
I was referring to the part that says,
‎当出现生物恐怖主义威胁时 ‎你们要尽快保障人民安全
when there's a bioterrorism threat, you haul ass to keep people safe.
‎到那时不要再想什么政治影响
Political blowback be damned.
‎操纵进行中的犯罪调查
Manipulating an ongoing criminal investigation
‎会给你带来麻烦的 马斯
can come back to bite you, Mars.
‎我们已经在监视布朗顿 ‎我们可以等一等
We have Brunton under surveillance. We can wait it out.
‎我理解联邦调查局是个独立机构
I understand the FBI is an independent organization.
‎但你们生物恐怖袭击的调查 ‎真的是一塌糊涂
But you guys really shit the bed on this bioterror investigation.
‎我想我们说完了
I think we're done here.
‎那个不知是什么的疾病 ‎没有在休斯顿蔓延的唯一原因
The only reason there wasn't a pandemic of God-knows-what in Houston
‎是汉娜威尔士 ‎在联邦调查局停止调查后
was because Hannah Wells wouldn't let it go
‎不愿放弃 她为此献出了生命
when the FBI shut it down. It cost her her life.
‎如果从现在起到选举日期间 ‎发生另一次袭击
If there is another attack between now and election day,
‎都是你的责任
it's on you.
‎你好
Hello.
‎我只是去弄点咖啡 ‎刚刚没在看你睡觉
Uh, I'm just going to get some coffee. I was not watching you sleep.
‎别烦我了
Stop bothering me.
‎骚扰电话
Telemarketer?
‎更糟
Worse.
‎是罗琳
Lorraine.
‎她一直来烦我
She keeps hounding me
‎让我今天和亚伦 ‎一起出席佛罗里达的竞选活动
to go on today's campaign swing through Florida with Aaron.
‎-撑一撑场面 ‎-你会去吗
-To keep up appearances. -Will you?
‎我以为你不应该掺和选举的事呢
I thought you weren't supposed to involve yourself in campaign issues.
‎嘿 现在是我的私人时间 ‎我只是个表示关切的一般市民
Hey, I'm on my personal time here. I'm just an ordinary concerned citizen.
‎不 我不会去
No, I'm not going.
‎追加提问
Follow-up question.
‎不是我不想让你在我这住 但…
Not that I don't love having you as a houseguest, but...
‎你们还有和好的机会吗
is there any chance you guys will get back together?
‎没有
No.
‎我知道让你扮演 ‎支持男友的好伴侣并不公平
I know it's unfair to ask you to play the role of the supportive good spouse,
‎-但柯克曼在佛罗里达快输了 ‎-赛斯…
-but Kirkman's down in Florida. -Seth...
‎他要因为亚伦的所作所为
It just sucks that he has to suffer collateral damage
‎而承受连带损失 这让人难过
because of what Aaron did.
‎真的有那么糟糕吗
Was it really that bad?
‎他和艾米丽上床了
He slept with Emily.
‎让那个混蛋去死吧 不要为他助选
Yeah, fuck that asshole. You're not campaigning for him.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎联邦探员 不许动
Federal agents. Do not move!
‎搞什么
What the fuck?
‎-菲尔布朗顿 ‎-你们不能就这样闯进我家
-Phil Brunton? -You can't just break into my home.
‎我们有不敲门逮捕令 可以直接进入
We may enter unannounced with a no-knock warrant.
‎穿上衣服跟我走
Get dressed and come with me.
‎-最新数字来了 ‎-好
-Latest numbers are in. - Okay.
‎柯克曼在内华达落后四个点
Kirkman is trailing behind by four points in Nevada,
‎在亚利桑那和田纳西分别是三个点
and three in Arizona and Tennessee.
‎该死我得想办法 ‎把一些紫色变成金色
Damn it! I've got to turn some of this purple to gold.
‎你跟点物成金的麦德斯正相反
You're like a reverse Midas.
‎去怪送信的人吧 拜托了
Shoot the messenger, please.
‎如果这些数字保持不变 ‎我们就赢不了
If these numbers hold, there is no path to victory.
‎在他的故乡有什么变化吗
Is there any movement in his home state?
‎没有 看起来纽约还是会投给波特
No, looks like New York's still going to Porter.
‎去他的纽约
Well, screw New York.
‎如果他们要继续跪舔民主党
If they're gonna keep sucking Democrat balls,
‎那我就不再在他们身上 ‎浪费我宝贵的资金了
then I'm not wasting any more of my precious funds on them.
‎太晚了 总统明天会去做简短活动
Too late. POTUS is doing a whistle-stop there tomorrow.
‎代我向百老汇问好 纽约行程取消了
Give my regards to Broadway. We're scuttling that New York trip.
‎我们要让他去还有机会赢的地方
Let's reroute him some place where he has a chance.
‎休斯顿事件后 ‎德克萨斯的数据有小幅上升
There was a small uptick in Texas after the Houston incident.
‎-对不起 你喝多了吗 ‎-哦 天啊声音开大点
-I'm sorry. Are you high? - Oh, my God! Turn it up.
‎现已确认菲尔布朗顿
It's now confirmed that Phil Brunton,
‎莫斯总统竞选的国内事务首席策略家
the chief domestic strategist for the Moss presidential campaign,
‎今晨被联邦探员拘捕
was taken into custody by federal agents early this morning.
‎指控与上周未遂的生物恐怖袭击有关
The charges related to last week's attempted bioterror attack.
‎十月惊喜 朋友 ‎莫斯现在前途未卜了
Whoo-hoo! October surprise, bitches. All bets are off for Moss now.
‎德克萨斯的角逐正式开始了
Texas is officially in play!
‎奥尔巴尼的表演艺术中心外形像颗蛋
The Performing Arts Center in Albany is shaped like an egg.
‎我能看看吗
Can I see?
‎像被切了一半的蛋 ‎我们今天能去看吗
Like an egg sliced in half. Do we get to see it today?
‎很遗憾 宝贝 现在竞选活动的节奏
Unfortunately, sweetheart, the campaign is moving at a sprinter's pace
‎就像马拉松最后一公里的冲刺 ‎奥尔巴尼没能成为最后的目的地之一
in the 26th mile of a marathon. And Albany did not make the cut.
‎不管能不能看到蛋 ‎这都会是场很棒的旅行 小潘
Well, egg or no egg, we'll have a great trip, Pen.
‎你紧张吗
Are you nervous?
‎-并没有 ‎-她太冷静了 不会紧张
-Not really. -She's too cool to be nervous.
‎你呢对于要在曼哈顿介绍我 ‎你紧张吗
How about you? Are you nervous about introducing me in Manhattan?
‎我有很多朋友会到场支持我 ‎这会有些帮助
Well, I have a lot of friends there coming to support me, so that helps.
‎你看上去很累 没事吧
You look tired. Is everything okay?
‎我都不知道昨晚有没有合眼
I'm not even sure if I closed my eyes last night.
‎失眠者的梦就是普通人的睡眠
An insomniac's dream is a regular person's sleep.
‎嘿吼 早上好
Hey-ho, good morning.
‎我们和一个州有个约会 ‎她的名字叫德克萨斯
We got a date with a state and her name is Texas.
‎-女士们 能给我点时间吗 ‎-我们正要走
-Ladies, can I have a second? -We were just leaving.
‎回头见
See you later.
‎纽约怎么了
What happened to New York?
‎菲尔布朗顿的事 ‎德克萨斯的事情不要和我吵
Phil Brunton happened. Don't fight me on Texas.
‎莫斯摔倒了 要是不趁他倒下时
Moss has fallen, and we would be remiss
‎踢他两脚 就是我们的不对了
if we didn't kick him a little while he's down.
‎我还没想明白 他可能知情吗
I still can't wrap my head around this. Could he have known?
‎以我与他共事的经验来看不会
The Moss I worked for? No.
‎但为了胜利 他会不择手段 ‎你一定要让这件事看上去都是他的错
But he'd do anything to win, and you've got to make this all about him.
‎-他没有受牵连 ‎-恐怖分子的薪水是他发的
-He hasn't been implicated. -He signed the terrorist's paycheck.
‎这也不代表他知情
Still doesn't mean he knew.
‎他的双手是沾着血的
His hands are bloody,
‎无论他是手持利刃还是握过沾血的手
whether he held the knife or shook the hand of the guy who did.
‎你在演讲里要说清楚
You've gotta hammer that home in your speech.
‎如果你能拿下德克萨斯 ‎亚伦能拿下佛罗里达…
If you swing Texas and Aaron swings Florida...
‎-我们就能有机会 ‎-不只是机会 亲爱的
-We've got a shot. -More than a shot, hon.
‎你就能赢
You win.
‎她为什么拒绝吃止痛药让她接电话
Why is she refusing to take her pain meds? Put her on the phone.
‎嘿
Hey.
‎妈妈 怎么回事
Mom, what's going on?
‎你知道那个药会让我昏昏沉沉
You know what a fog that medication puts me in.
‎是 但也不会那么痛
Yes, a relatively painless one.
‎我想今晚保持头脑清醒等你回家 ‎这样我们能聊聊
I wanna be clear-headed tonight when you get home, so we can talk.
‎-我现在就回家 ‎-不 不要
-Uh... I'm coming home now. -No, don't.
‎-你有工作要做 ‎-如果你不吃药
-You have work to do. -If you don't take your meds,
‎-我必须现在回家 ‎-天啊
-I have to come home right now. -For Pete's sake.
‎又不是什么大事 我只是想清醒一次
It's nothing earth-shattering. I just wanna be lucid for once.
‎也许能在看 ‎《危险边缘》问答时赢你
Maybe beat you at Jeopardy.
‎我会吃药的
I'll take the damn pills.
‎-你保证 ‎-保证 好好工作
-You promise? -Yes. Have a good day at work.
‎我会把我们 ‎影响投资计划的数据分析转给你
I'll forward you the data analytics from our impact investing initiative.
‎嘿 我想为罗琳道歉 ‎你不必去佛罗里达
Hey. Look, I wanna apologize for Lorraine. You don't have to go to Florida.
‎我知道我不必去 但我会去的
I know I don't. But I'm going anyway.
‎-真的 ‎-不是为了你 蠢货
-Really? -Not for you, pendejo.
‎我是为了总统而去
I'm going for POTUS.
‎好吗他没有理由 ‎因为你破坏竞选誓言而受牵连
Okay? There's no reason he should suffer for your broken campaign promises.
‎-伊莎 谢谢你 这… ‎-听我说
-Isi, thank you, this-- -Listen to me.
‎-你要遵守以下规则 知道吗 ‎-好
-Here are the ground rules, okay? - Yeah.
‎在公开场合 我们是 ‎世界上最幸福的情侣
In public, we're the world's happiest couple.
‎一旦下台 你不能摸我
The second we're offstage, you don't touch me,
‎不要跟我说话 你对我来说不存在
you don't talk to me, you don't exist.
‎好 都听你的 好的
Fine, yeah, whatever you need. All right.
‎-艾米丽去吗 ‎-不 她母亲不行了
-Is Emily going? -No. No, her mom is close to the end.
‎上次她母亲快死的时候 ‎她用这个借口跟你上了床
Well, the last time her mother was dying, she used it as an excuse to fuck you.
‎很好 我很期待见到你
Great. I am looking forward to meeting you.
‎-8点半见 ‎-对不起
-I'll... I'll see you at 8:30. -Sorry.
‎好吧 好的 ‎嘿 你知道我长什么样吗
All right, sounds good. Hey, do you know what I look like?
‎对 当然
Oh, right, of course.
‎到时见 再见
Uh, I'll see you then. Bye.
‎-约会 ‎-不是
-A date? -Uh, no.
‎那是我女儿的妈妈
That was my daughter's mother.
‎丝黛芬妮的妈妈
Stephanie's mom?
‎你要跟21年前 ‎买了你精子的女人吃晚饭
You're having dinner with the woman who bought your sperm 21 years ago?
‎-那就太奇怪了 我们是一起喝东西 ‎-好吧 丝黛芬妮去吗
-That'd be weird. We're having drinks. -Okay. Is Stephanie gonna be there?
‎不去 我上次见她还是辩论之前
No. I haven't heard from her since before the debates.
‎你能相信布朗顿这事吗
Oh, can you believe this Brunton thing?
‎莫斯一定知情
Moss had to know about it.
‎…卑鄙、穷途末路的柯克曼竞选团队
...despicable, last-ditch effort of the failing Kirkman campaign
‎败局已定 只能靠 ‎伪造阴谋来争取胜利
to win the election the only way he can, by fabricating wild conspiracies.
‎去你的
Fuck off.
‎我真不敢相信 ‎他想把柯克曼卷进来 最疯狂的是…
I can't believe he's trying to spin Kirkman into this. The craziest thing--
‎-你跟亚伦睡了 ‎-什么
-You slept with Aaron? -What?
‎-怎么回事罗琳的八卦 ‎-伊莎贝尔告诉我的
-What is that? Some Lorraine gossip? -Isabel told me.
‎-哦 我的天 她跟所有人都说了 ‎-她只告诉了我
-Oh, my God. She's telling everyone? -I'm the only one she told.
‎-怎么 你俩现在是闺蜜了 ‎-艾米 你为什么这么做
-What, are you two, like, besties now? -Em. Why'd you do it?
‎我不是找借口
Look, it's not an excuse,
‎但那是我人生中最糟糕的一天
but that was one of the worst days of my life.
‎我刚知道我母亲的癌症扩散了
I had just found out that my mom's cancer had spread
‎她想自杀 然后…
and that she wanted to kill herself, and...
‎那时我已想不到任何后果 ‎因为那就是世界末日
in the moment, there were no consequences because it felt like the end of the world.
‎-那个生物武器和我们想的不一样 ‎-你在说什么
-The bioweapon isn't what we thought. - What are you talking about?
‎我已经分析完了 ‎蒙伯格自杀前上传的基因序列
I finished sequencing the genetic code Momberg uploaded before he killed himself.
‎病毒不是设计用来杀害有色人种的
The virus wasn't designed to kill people of color?
‎不是 不是杀害他们
No, not to kill them.
‎那是做什么
What does it do?
‎某种意义上说更阴险
In some ways, something even more insidious.
‎大规模绝育
Mass sterilization?
‎看起来这就是预期结果
That appears to have been the intended outcome.
‎生物武器化的流感将进入
The bioweaponized flu was going to be introduced into populations
‎少数族群增长率高的人群
with high minority growth rates.
‎大部分人口会被感染
Large swaths of the population would become infected,
‎但然后他们会恢复
but then they'd get better.
‎无法检测到的是 ‎流感经过基因序列改造
What would be undetectable was that it had been genetically sequenced
‎会让少数族裔宿主被绝育
to sterilize its minority hosts.
‎所以这是一个 ‎改变选民人口组成的长期计划
So this is a long-term plan to change the demographic of the electorate.
‎压制选民的工程
Engineered voter suppression.
‎但等一下 如果他们是在做长期打算
But, wait, if they're playing the long game,
‎那这对这次选举不会有影响
this would have no effect on the election.
‎也就是说莫斯没有动机
Which means Moss would have no motive.
‎只有保护国家政治形势的遗赠
Just the legacy of protecting the political landscape of the country.
‎先生 美国人民有权获知此事
Sir, the American people have a right to be told about this.
‎如果现在公布消息 ‎会被当成政治策略
If we release this now, it'd just be considered a political ploy.
‎没人会相信 我都很难相信
No one would believe it. Hell, I'm having a hard time believing it.
‎别忘了 基因序列曾短暂出现在网上
Don't forget, the genetic code was briefly on the Web.
‎幸运的话 下载者只是出于科学好奇
If we're lucky, it was downloaded out of scientific curiosity
‎没有搞种族灭绝的信念
of a non-genocidal persuasion.
‎无论如何 消息很快会传开
Regardless, the news is going to get out. Soon.
‎我要强调 ‎武器化的病毒从未散播出去
And I stress, the weaponized virus was never released.
‎我们现在已经度过潜伏期
We are now past the incubation period
‎我们没有接到 ‎感染案例的报告 也就是说
and there are no reported cases of infection, meaning,
‎谢天谢地 ‎我们当中受非色素影响的人
thankfully, for those of us in the non-pigmentally challenged category,
‎没有被绝育 提问
-no cases of sterilization. Questions? -
‎赛斯 如果技术已经流出 ‎威胁依然存在
Seth, if the technology is out there, the threat still exists.
‎当然 和其他针对人类的威胁一样
Of course, along with every other known threat to humanity,
‎大多数在网上都能找到
most of which are available on the Web.
‎我们在密切监控事态 ‎任何想使用它的人都该小心了
We're monitoring the situation closely. Woe to anyone who tries to use it.
‎-丹尼斯 ‎-有证据显示莫斯参与其中吗
-Dennis. -Is there evidence that Moss is involved?
‎让我用一个问题来回答你
Let me answer that question with a question.
‎菲尔布朗顿有资源
Did Phil Brunton have the resources
‎独自实现这种量级的阴谋吗
to pull off something of this magnitude alone?
‎总统认为布朗顿 ‎在和外部团队合作吗
Does the president believe Brunton was working with an outside group?
‎据我所知 柯克曼总统不知道
As far as I know, President Kirkman has no knowledge
‎任何外部组织参与其中
of any outside group involved in the matter.
‎所以他认为这是内部策划 ‎来自莫斯竞选团队内部
So he believes this was an inside job? From within the Moss campaign?
‎如大家所知 根据《哈奇法案》
As you know, the Hatch Act prevents me
‎我不得就与竞选相关事宜发表言论
from commenting on matters related to the campaign.
‎我只想知道他的本能反应 赛斯
I just want his gut reaction, Seth.
‎总统认为莫斯参与其中了吗
Does the president think Moss was involved?
‎莫斯的国内政策专家已经被捕
The engineer of Moss' domestic policy has been arrested
‎罪名据称是通过颠覆选民的人口组成
for allegedly trying to end democracy as we know it
‎为莫斯党派谋取利益
by tipping the demographics of the electorate
‎终结我们的民主 ‎要我再给你解释一遍吗
in favor of Moss' party. Do I really need to spell it out for you?
‎做得好
Nicely done!
‎-我激动到要高潮 ‎-谢谢
-I kinda got a lady chub. -Oh, thank you.
‎莫斯的竞选中心阵脚大乱
They're shitting bricks over at Moss' campaign headquarters.
‎我刚结束 你怎么知道的
I just finished. How do you know that?
‎是 开始准备 ‎针对莫斯下一步行动的回应
Yeah, so start preparing responses to what Moss is gonna do next.
‎他会否认任何关联
He's gonna deny any involvement.
‎对找出任何 ‎他赞美他老朋友菲尔的录音
Yeah! So pull together any sound bites of him praising his old friend Phil,
‎因为他会表现得像不认识他一样
'cause he's gonna act like he doesn't know the guy.
‎就好像在队列中 他都认不出他
Like he couldn't pick him out of a lineup.
‎他怎么能这么说菲尔是高级顾问
How could he claim that? Phil was a senior advisor.
‎-他… ‎-我可以 也确实要明确表态
-He's-- - I can and I do
‎我不知道也未参与
unequivocally state that I had no knowledge of,
‎任何危害美国人民的计划
or involvement in, any plan to harm American citizens.
‎-布朗顿先生… ‎-来了
-And while Mr. Brunton... -Here we go.
‎…在被证明有罪前必须假定为无罪…
...must be presumed innocent until proven guilty...
‎等着吧
Wait for it.
‎…我必须说 我并不十分了解他
...I have to say that I didn't know him very well.
‎我真想留下看媒体疯狂报道
Oh, I wish I could stay for the press-feeding frenzy,
‎但我要出发去德克萨斯了
but I've gotta leave for Texas.
‎当蒂快点 空军一号不会等你
Dontae! 脕ndale. Air Force One ain't gonna wait for you.
‎-当蒂 帮个忙 ‎-尽管说
-Dontae, do me a favor. -Anything.
‎-盯着罗琳 ‎-尽管说 但这个除外
-Keep an eye on Lorraine. -Anything but that.
‎我知道她在莫斯团队有间谍
I know she has a mole in the Moss campaign.
‎你多留点心
Just keep your eyes and ears open.
‎它可以在半空中加油 ‎还有一整个手术室
It can refuel in mid-air and it has a whole operating room.
‎它装备了军事防御系统 以防遇袭
It's packed with military defense systems in case we're attacked.
‎亲爱的 萨莎可能不想 ‎在我们起飞前听到这些
Honey, Sasha might not wanna hear about that stuff right before we fly.
‎你们好 女士们 你看起来棒极了
Well, hello, ladies. Don't you look fabulous.
‎我差点就穿了一模一样的裙子 ‎还好我没穿
I almost wore that exact same skirt. I'm glad I didn't.
‎你一定会赢得“谁穿最好看”奖
You would've won "Who Wore It Best"
‎-而我最讨厌输了 ‎-这是我雇她的唯一原因
-and I hate to lose at anything. -Only reason I hired her.
‎-嘿 我能占用你一点时间吗 ‎-好
-Hey, can I steal you away for a second? - Yeah.
‎亲爱的 起飞后 ‎也许你可以带萨莎参观一下
Sweetheart, after we take off, maybe you can give Sasha the grand tour.
‎汤姆萨莎来干什么
Tom! What is Sasha doing here?
‎请她在集会上介绍我 ‎是你让我叫她来帮忙的
The favor of introducing me at the rally, which you asked me to get her to do.
‎是 那是计划去曼哈顿的时候
Yeah, when we were scheduled to appear in Manhattan.
‎-休斯顿不是曼哈顿 ‎-如今也不是上个世纪了
-Houston is not Manhattan. -It's also not the last century.
‎你觉得跨性别问题在那里 ‎会引起什么反响
And how do you think the transgender issue is gonna play down there?
‎供你参考 ‎休斯顿更偏向自由 而非保守
For your edification, Houston leans more liberal than conservative.
‎那你去郊区看看呢
Until you get to the suburbs.
‎别把所有保守党都想成一个样
Please stop painting all Conservatives with the same brush.
‎芭芭拉布什后来也理解了跨性别问题
Barbara Bush came to understand transgender issues,
‎而她曾生活在休斯顿
and she lived in Houston.
‎休斯顿是 ‎反跨性别卫生间运动的诞生地
Houston is the birthplace of the anti-trans bathroom movement.
‎你想让我怎么办
What do you want me to do?
‎走过去 把我小姨子扔下飞机
March down there and throw my sister-in-law off the plane?
‎我们是要去莫斯的地盘 ‎让他的德州同胞反对他
We're going to Moss' home turf to try to turn his fellow Texans against him.
‎为什么 汤姆为什么要给他的阵营 ‎提供可以反击的弱点
Why, Tom? Why hand his base something to attack back against?
‎我们准备好要起飞了 ‎你最好去找个座位
We're getting ready to take off. You should probably go find a seat.
佛罗里达州 奥兰多
‎真的假的
Really?
‎我发誓这和我无关 ‎我告诉过罗琳 我们要双床房
I swear I had nothing to do with this. I told Lorraine we needed a two-bedroom.
‎如果她认为 ‎这会有个电影般的浪漫结局
If she thinks this is gonna lead to a romcom ending,
‎-我要好好给她剧透一下 ‎-我睡沙发就好
-I've got a big spoiler alert for her. -I'll just take the couch.
‎祝你愉快
- -Have fun.
‎什么怎么了
What? What's wrong?
‎机票能退吗
Are the tickets refundable?
‎不 爸爸 我们当然想见你
No, Papi, of course we wanna see you.
‎只是…亚伦的会见日程都满了
It's just... Aaron is booked solid with appearances.
‎我们不希望你们大老远从波多黎各来
We would hate for you to come all the way from Puerto Rico
‎却没时间陪你们
and not have any time to spend with you.
‎好吧 是 我们会想办法
Okay. Yeah, we'll work it out.
‎他也等不及要见你们
He can't wait to meet you either.
‎好的 旅途顺利
Okay, have a safe flight.
‎你还没告诉你父母 我们分手了
You haven't told your parents we broke up.
‎还没来得及
Hadn't gotten around to it yet.
‎已经有一阵子了 你刚刚就可以说
It's been a while. Could've done it just now.
‎如果我们的关系不是国家机密的话
If only our relationship status weren't state secret.
‎你什么都和你妈说的
You tell your mother everything.
‎我试过告诉他们
I tried to tell them.
‎但是呢
But?
‎我不断拖延 ‎想等到能不用哭着说的时候再说
I kept putting it off until I could do it without crying.
‎失陪
Excuse me.
‎我意识到我还没问过你
I realized that I didn't even ask you how you felt
‎对于明天在休斯顿登台感觉如何
about taking the stage in Houston tomorrow.
‎说实话吗紧张
Honestly? Nervous.
‎我本该告诉你换场地的事
I should have told you about the venue change,
‎-如果你想退出… ‎-也很兴奋
-and if you wanna back out-- -And excited.
‎这其实是个更大的机会
I mean, it's actually a much bigger opportunity.
‎我的介绍讲的都是你 但让我来做…
My intro will be all about you, but just the fact of me doing it...
‎如果我能哪怕让一个人 ‎觉得跨性别者是正常人也好…
If I can normalize transgender for even one person...
‎汤姆 怎么了
Tom, what?
‎我需要你明白 个人来说 ‎我很骄傲能让你来介绍我
I need you to understand that, personally, I am so proud that you would introduce me.
‎继续说
Go on.
‎但离选举只剩几天了 ‎由于天降的机遇
But the election's in a few days, and with this gift that I've been given,
‎莫斯阵营发生的这一切
everything that's happening in the Moss campaign,
‎让我有了赢的希望
I've actually got a shot at winning this thing.
‎但策略上来说…
But, strategically...
‎你不是帮我做介绍的最佳人选
you're not the best person to help me do that.
‎萨莎 我很抱歉
Sasha, I am so sorry.
‎但如果我们能赢下这场选举 ‎我可以帮助做出改变
But if we can win this election, I can help change things.
‎在更大的层面上
I mean, in a really big way.
‎我理解
I understand.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎嘿 妈妈
Hey, Mom.
‎-缇娜呢 ‎-我让她回家了
-Where's Tina? -I sent her home.
‎你没吃止疼药
You didn't take your pain meds.
‎不
No.
‎-不 ‎-对 就是今晚
-No. -Yeah. Tonight's the night.
‎妈妈 求你别这样
Mom, please don't do this.
‎过来 宝贝
Come here, baby.
‎过来坐到我身边
Come sit next to me.
‎妈妈
Mom.
‎你知道我爱你 对吗
Oh, you know I love you, right?
‎不知道
No.
‎你必须留下一段时间 ‎向我证明这一点
You're gonna have to stick around a while and convince me.
‎没有哪个母亲会比我更自豪
No mother could ever be prouder.
‎我在离世时 心里知道 ‎我孕育了一个很特别的生命
I can leave this world knowing I created something really special.
‎生下你是我做过的最棒的事
You're the best thing I ever did.
‎我只有一件后悔的事
I just have one regret.
‎什么
What?
‎我给了你一个特别混蛋的父亲
That I gave you such an asshole for a father.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
‎是我不好
It's my bad.
‎你不仅弥补了他的位置 还做了更多
You more than made up for him.
‎还有几天就选举了
The election's only a few days away.
‎我以为你能撑到选举后
I thought you were gonna hold on until after.
‎我知道 宝贝 我尽力了
I know, baby. I tried.
‎但我做不到
But I can't.
‎我知道我让你做的事看起来很糟糕
I know what I'm asking you to do seems awful.
‎但如果我能选择离开的方式
But if I could choose how I wanted to go,
‎能幸福死去的方式
how I could die happy,
‎那就是平静地
it would be peacefully,
‎躺在这世上我最爱的人的怀抱里
in the arms of the one I love the most in this world.
‎你是这世上唯一一个能帮我的人
You are the only person on Earth who can give me that.
‎嘿 出什么事了
Hey, something wrong?
‎此时此刻 什么事都没有
At this moment, absolutely nothing.
‎我已经记不得 ‎上次流下幸福的泪水是什么时候
I can't remember the last time I cried because I was happy.
‎我不知道具体日期 但肯定是
I don't know the exact date, but it was definitely around
‎我在床上表现超凡的某一天
one of my more spectacular performances in bed.
‎谢谢你抽时间陪我 我知道你有多忙
Thank you for carving out time for me. I know how crazed you are.
‎运营白宫 加上你的业余活动
The madness of running the White House, your extracurricular activities.
‎我不是说那个
Oh. I wasn't talking about that.
‎那个已经解决了 都过去了
We have worked through that. We've moved on.
‎业余活动
By extracurricular activities,
‎我是指你协助曝光的大型药企的丑闻
I was talking about the Big Pharma scandal that you helped expose.
‎它还在导致伤亡
You know, it's still claiming casualties.
‎我听说加略特德特维尔被要求
I've heard Garrett Detwiler has been asked to resign
‎从至少三个董事会辞职
from at least three boards he sits on.
‎那边有个沙发
There's a couch over there,
‎不过我们不如回家庆祝吧
but why don't we just go home and celebrate?
‎好啊
Oh, yes, please.
‎很好
That's good.
‎我爱你
I love you.
‎谢谢你 宝贝
Thank you, baby.
‎抱歉
Excuse me.
‎-请给我账单 好吗谢谢 ‎-好
-Can I have the bill, please? Thank you. - Sure.
‎赛斯
Seth?
‎-你不会是瑞亚吧 ‎-就是我
-You can't be Riya. -And yet I am.
‎你来早了
You got here early.
‎其实 你…
Uh, actually, you're...
‎你和我想象的不一样
You're not what I had pictured.
‎-你想象中是什么样 ‎-不知道 我妈那样
-What were you picturing? -I don't know. My mom?
‎差太远了
I was way off.
‎能麻烦你先别结账吗你要点什么
Can you actually leave it open for me? What can I get you?
‎-一杯哈维撞墙 ‎-就来
A Harvey Wallbanger.
‎-抱歉 我以为你在开玩笑 ‎-不是 你的笑声和丝黛芬妮一样
-Sorry, I thought you were joking. -No, you have Stephanie's laugh.
‎其实应该是她的笑声像我 对吧
Well, actually, she would have my laugh, right?
‎哦 天啊 她遗传了我的笑声
Oh, man, she inherited my laugh.
‎她听到傻事的时候就这样笑
When she hears something silly.
‎那我要让她笑一笑 ‎如果还能再见到她的话
I'll have to make her laugh, then. Presuming I see her again.
‎她在大学太忙了 大四了
She's been so busy at college. It's her senior year, you know.
‎她会以优秀毕业生的身份毕业
She'll be graduating summa cum laude.
‎嘿 我在哈佛也是优秀毕业生
Hey, I graduated summa cum laude, at Harvard.
‎抱歉 人们总取笑我
Sorry, people always make fun of me
‎说我会不经意透露自己读过哈佛
for slipping in the fact that I went to Harvard.
‎不用道歉
Don't apologize.
‎哈佛是我选你精子的原因
Harvard is the reason I chose your sperm.
‎他们都这么说 开玩笑
-That's what they all say. Just kidding. -
‎是丝黛芬妮申请的法学院之一
It's one of the law schools Stephanie's applied to.
‎-她要上法学院 ‎-如果能录取的话
-She's going to law school? -If she gets in.
‎怎么会不录取
Why wouldn't she?
‎她的成绩和课外活动足够了 但现在
She's got the grades and the extracurriculars, but nowadays,
‎申请里一定要有能脱颖而出的材料
you have to pack that application with stuff that really stands out.
‎白宫有实习机会吗
Does the White House have internships?
‎有 可以在网站上申请
Yeah, the application's on the website.
‎我想那些机会都会给有推荐人的人
I assume those spots go to people who have connections.
‎妈妈
Mom?
‎妈妈 能听见吗
Mom, can you hear me?
‎妈妈
Mom?
‎这里是911 有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
‎我需要救护车
I need an ambulance. I need an ambulance.
‎哦 天啊
Oh, my God!
‎妈妈
Mom.
‎巴比妥过量 病人无反应
Barbiturate OD. Patient is unresponsive.
‎我需要贝美格和IV纳洛酮
I need bemegride and IV naloxone.
‎给我一个公称直径管、血糖和活性炭
Get me a DN tube, blood glucose and activated carbon.
‎准备好了听我数 一、二、三
When we're ready and on my count. One, two, three.
‎-我们知道她具体吃了什么吗 ‎-女儿说是戊巴比妥
-Do we know exactly what she took? -Daughter says pentobarbital.
‎她出现心室纤维性颤动
- She's gone into V-fib.
‎你母亲有签署放弃抢救协议吗
Does your mother have a DNR?
‎你们能救救她吗
Can you just save her?
‎你知道她有预立过遗嘱吗
Do you know if she has advanced directive?
‎你是医生 你发过誓的
You're a doctor. You took an oath!
‎-能请你救救她吗 ‎-女士 我需要你回答我
-Can you please just save her? -Miss, I need an answer.
‎-我不知道我对她做了什么 ‎-你母亲签过放弃抢救协议吗
- I don't know what I did to her! -Does your mother have a DNR?
‎她签过
Yes, she does.
‎对不起 妈妈
I'm so sorry, Mom.
‎您正在收看《华盛顿一号》
You're watching DC One.
‎我是萨拉托加斯普林斯的泰德
Ted from Saratoga Springs.
‎我想感谢柯克曼总统 ‎阻止了针对我们民主制度的袭击
I just wanna thank President Kirkman for stopping the attack on our democracy.
‎我是来自俄亥俄的比尔
Bill from Ohio.
‎你知道谁有权力安排这一切吗
You know who had the power to orchestrate it?
‎那个非法的混蛋柯克曼…
That illegitimate son-of-a-prick Kirkman...
‎比尔 注意用词 巴吞鲁日的拉莫纳
Bill, language. Ramona from Baton Rouge.
‎在我再次为莫斯总统投票前
Before I vote again for President Moss,
‎我需要知道他有没有参与这场骚乱
I need to know if he's wrapped up in this mess or not.
‎美国人民有…
-The American people have a-- -
‎-喂 ‎-你在看《华盛顿一号》吗
- Hello? -Are you watching DC One?
‎总统先生 现在是凌晨4点
Mr. President, it's 4:00 a.m.
‎没人在看《华盛顿一号》
Nobody's watching DC One right now.
‎我知道你会坚持你的合法建议
I know you're gonna stand by your legal advice
‎让我别干预调查 但我觉得
for me to stay out of the investigation, but I think it's ridiculous
‎我只能从电视新闻获得信息很荒唐
that the only information I'm getting on it is coming from cable news.
‎我需要知道莫斯有没有参与其中
I need to know whether Moss was involved or not.
‎您说得对 先生 我坚持我的建议
You're right, sir. I do stand by my advice.
‎-我帮您梳理一下 ‎-没必要 我懂
-Let me walk you through it. -You don't need to. I get it.
‎作为候选人 这样有违职业道德 ‎甚至可能涉嫌腐败
As a candidate, I could appear unethical, possibly even corrupt.
‎但作为美国总统 ‎我觉得我在玩忽职守
But as president of the United States, I feel I'm being negligent,
‎我很难在两者间平衡
and I'm having a difficult time reconciling the two.
‎先生 要相信联邦调查局
Sir, have faith in the FBI.
‎您帮帮忙 也睡会儿觉吧
And for God's sake, get some sleep.
‎我也希望我能睡
I wish I could.
‎这和她见教皇时比都不算什么
That was nothing compared to the time she met the Pope.
‎妈妈 不要说
Ay, Mama, no.
‎-等等 你见过教皇 ‎-她吐在他身上了
- Wait, you met the Pope? -She threw up on him.
‎我当时才一岁
I was one.
‎那是教皇第一次 ‎也是最后一次到访波多黎各
The Pope's first and last visit to Puerto Rico.
‎-听着… ‎-喷射式呕吐
- Look-- -Projectile vomit.
‎她见到总统时做了一模一样的事
She did exactly the same thing when she met the president.
‎你们俩什么时候入住海军天文台
So when exactly do you two move into the Naval Observatory?
‎你们知道那是副总统的住处吧
You do know that's where the vice president lives?
‎好吧 先别想那么远
Okay, let's not count our chickens.
‎我在看网上的图片
I've been checking pictures online,
‎有间房特别适合做宝宝的房间
and there's a room that would make a perfect nursery,
‎如果接下来四年你们有了宝宝 ‎可以派上用场
should any babies appear in the next four years.
‎如果莫斯的生物恐怖袭击成功了
Well, if Moss' bioterror attack had succeeded,
‎哪里都不会有拉丁裔宝宝出生
there'd be no Latino babies appearing anywhere.
‎背后是莫斯操纵的
So Moss was behind it?
‎-我们还不知道 ‎-他雇了菲尔布朗顿做决策者
-Well, we don't know that. -He hired Phil Brunton as policymaker.
‎他的决策就是种族灭绝
His policy is genocide.
‎人们还会投票给莫斯吗
Will people still vote for Moss?
‎遗憾的是 他的支持者会
Sadly, his base will.
‎但我觉得他们遗忘了 ‎自己所继承的东西的重要性…
But I think that people who've lost touch with the importance of their heritage...
‎我很羞愧 在遇到你们的女儿之前
I am ashamed to admit I may have been one of them
‎我可能也是他们当中的一员
before I met your daughter.
‎我想现在他们看明白了
I think now they're opening their eyes.
‎他们意识到 ‎把我们看作另外一个群体
They're realizing that people who just regard us as the other group
‎不当作美国人的人 不值得获得选票
and not as fellow Americans, they just don't deserve our vote.
‎阿门
Amen.
‎如果我们能投票 我们一定会投给你
You'd certainly have our vote, if we could vote.
‎波多黎各人在过去一百年间 ‎都是美国公民
Puerto Ricans have been US citizens for the past 100 years,
‎但依然不能投票
but we still can't vote.
‎政府收我们的钱 却不收我们的选票
The government takes our money but not our ballot.
‎这是我们当前体制最大的错误之一
It's one of the greatest failings of our current system,
‎如果我们能赢 我保证不会忘记这点
and one I promise not to forget if we win.
‎我们要迟到了
We are late.
‎亚伦要去争取一些能投票的人的选票
Aaron needs to go win over some people who actually can vote.
‎-很高兴见到你们 ‎-见到你真好
-It was such a pleasure meeting you. -It was wonderful to meet you.
‎-我很羞愧 ‎-为什么
-I am mortified. -About what?
‎-我不知道我妈妈联系了你 ‎-那很好啊 你妈妈很好
-I had no idea my mom had contacted you. -It was great. Your mother's great.
‎你好吗来 请坐
How are you? Here, have a seat.
‎我想当面道歉
Um... I just wanted to apologize in person.
‎丝黛芬妮 你不需要跟我道歉 ‎你没做错什么
Stephanie, you don't owe me an apology. You don't owe me anything.
‎我要为两件事跟你道歉
I owe you two apologies.
‎躲着不见你 我太不应该了
I was a total jerk for ghosting you.
‎不 你妈说了 你大学里很忙
No, your mother mentioned how busy college has been keeping you.
‎是 但那不是原因
It is, but that wasn't the reason.
‎-你不必… ‎-我父母去年离婚了
-You don't have to-- -My parents got divorced last year.
‎虽然我不是五岁小孩 但我也很难过
It's not like I was five, but I took it really hard.
‎为了泄愤 我做了DNA检测
I took a DNA test out of spite.
‎愚蠢地想着 他们不是我的亲生父母
Out of some silly fantasy that they weren't my real parents.
‎我根本没想到我猜对了一半
I didn't ever think that I'd be half right.
‎我的天 这样知道真相真糟糕
Oh, my God. What a terrible way to find out.
‎-他们从未告诉你 ‎-没有 都是我自己在探索
-They never told you? -Nope. It was a head trip.
‎然后我点击查看你是否在数据库中
Then I clicked to see if you were in the database,
‎同样 我从未想过你会在
again, never dreaming that you would be,
‎但你确实在
but you were.
‎然后你写信给我 从未想过我会回复
And then you wrote to me, never dreaming that I'd answer.
‎但我确实回复了
But I did.
‎每完成一步 我都受到一点惊吓
I had a small freak-out after every one of those steps.
‎最后一步时我吓傻了
The last one resulted in radio silence.
‎我很抱歉把你卷进来
I'm really sorry that I dragged you into this.
‎这对你不公平
It wasn't fair to you.
‎这是我所遇到的最好的事
This is the best thing that's ever happened to me.
‎你真的应该填写白宫实习的申请
And you really should fill out that White House internship application.
‎你有推荐人
You have connections.
‎你不必为我这么做 真的
You don't need to do that for me, seriously.
‎你能来 是白宫的荣幸
The White House would be lucky to have you.
‎那太棒了 谢谢
That would be amazing. Thank you.
‎-马上就好 马斯 ‎-不急 加略特
Oh. -Be right with you, Mars. -Take your time, Garrett.
‎我感谢你百忙之中抽空见我
I appreciate you squeezing me in like this.
‎如果你是来寻求资助 ‎我已经在支援另一位候选人了
If you're looking for a donation, I'm already backing another candidate.
‎不 我不是来要任何东西的
No, I'm not here to ask for anything.
‎你是代表总统来的吗
Are you here on behalf of the president?
‎不 是我自己要来
Nope. It's personal.
‎我只能想到这两个目的 ‎那你为什么要见我
Well, those are my only two guesses. Why do you need to see me?
‎我想告诉你 你是多烂的一个人渣
I wanted to tell you what a piece of shit you are.
‎你说什么
Excuse me?
‎还为了幸灾乐祸一下
And to gloat about the fact that you've been kicked off
‎你被踢出弗莱格坎德董事会 以及…
the board of FlagKind, and the board of directors--
‎如果你以为我会在乎离开几个董事会
If you think I give a flying piss about stepping down from a few boards,
‎那你比你现在看起来的样子还疯狂
you're even more insane than you look right now.
‎你还记得那个说 ‎你在任食品药品管理局局长期间
Do you remember that expos茅 about your corrupt practices
‎-腐败的爆料吗 ‎-谢谢你的到访 马斯
-when you were FDA commissioner? -Thanks for stopping by, Mars.
‎我想告诉你 爆料人是我
I wanted to let you know that it was me who exposed you.
‎抓住你了
Gotcha.
‎你那个上瘾的妻子怎样了 马斯
How's your addict wife, Mars? Hmm?
‎都是为这事 对不对
That's what this is all about, right?
‎我读到消息说 她曾去参加康复治疗
I read she went into rehab.
‎都是拜一种从不该进入市场的药所赐
Because of a drug that never should've been on the market,
‎都怪你让它进入市场
because you pushed it through.
‎责备我要比责备你那 ‎可悲的毒瘾妻子更容易 是不是
It's easier to blame me than your pathetic junkie wife, isn't it?
‎因为你在阿片类药物危机中的角色 ‎你该去坐牢
You should be in jail because of your part in the opioid crisis.
‎这永远不可能 马斯
Well, that's never gonna happen, Mars.
‎现在就出去
Now, get out.
‎但我需要知道 ‎因为你是莫斯最大的赞助商
And I do have to know, though, since you are Moss' biggest donor,
‎他参与生物恐怖袭击的阴谋了吗
was he part of the bioterror plot?
‎这是哪门子问题
What kind of question is that?
‎-你给我滚出我的办公室 ‎-好
-Yeah, you get out of my office! -Okay.
‎远离电脑
Step away from the computer.
‎-怎么回事 ‎-先生 我们需要您离开这里
- What's going on? -Sir, we need you to clear the area.
‎这是什么情况
What the hell is happening?
‎他们让布朗顿转为污点证人
They flipped Brunton.
‎德特维尔赞助了整个计划
Detwiler funded the whole thing.
‎加略特 如果你请不起律师 ‎我们会为你安排一位
Garrett, if you can't afford an attorney, one will be provided for you.
‎混蛋
Asshole.
‎如果有人想不起来 ‎就请从口袋里拿出一枚硬币
And should anyone need reminding, simply take a coin out of your pocket.
‎这个伟大国家建立的原则和座右铭
The principle and de facto motto
‎就在上面印着
on which this great nation was built is printed right there.
‎合众为一
E pluribus unum. Out of many, one.
‎黑人、白人、拉丁裔、亚裔 ‎我们都是移民
Black, white, Latino, Asian, we are all immigrants,
‎或移民的后裔
or descendants of immigrants,
‎我们组成了美国
and we are America!
‎正因此 我们是世界上最伟大的国家
It's what made us the greatest country on Earth,
‎这也将引领我们走向未来
and it is what will carry us into the future.
‎上帝保佑休斯顿 上帝保佑美国
God bless you, Houston. God bless America.
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎你做得很棒 我很为你骄傲
You did great. I am so proud of you.
‎怎么了嘿
What's wrong? Hey. Hey.
‎出什么事了
Did something happen?
‎我觉得萨莎应该和我们一起出席
I think Sasha should have been out there with us.
‎-我不敢相信你会这样对她 ‎-潘妮 对不起
-I can't believe you did that to her. -Penny, I'm sorry.
‎你知道我有多为萨莎阿姨骄傲
You know how proud I am of your Aunt Sasha.
‎在我看来并非如此
It doesn't look that way to me.
‎-你看上去以她为耻 ‎-当然不是
-It looks like you're ashamed of her. -Of course not. I...
‎我觉得这里有些人 ‎可能不会热情欢迎她
I felt that some of the people here might not give her a very warm reception.
‎那是因为他们不了解她
Only because they don't know her.
‎如果他们见到她 就会改变想法 ‎你没给他们这个机会
They'd change their minds if they met her. You didn't give them the chance.
‎-潘妮 拜托 ‎-重大新闻…
-Penny, please. - Humongous news--
‎-能给我们一点时间吗 ‎-这个消息太棒了
-Can you just give us a minute? -This is too good.
‎-德特维尔刚刚被捕了 ‎-他是莫斯最大的赞助人
-Detwiler was just arrested. -That's Moss' biggest donor.
‎还觉得莫斯没有参与吗
Still think Moss wasn't involved?
‎显然 我们要给 ‎你接下来的评论加点东西
Obviously, we're gonna add a topper to your next remarks.
‎这个电话得接 回头再聊
Ooh, I've gotta take this. I'm gonna catch up with you.
‎来吧 宝贝 我们走
Come on, honey, let's go.
‎所以要平时的两倍价
That's why this is gonna be twice the normal price.
‎迈尔斯 老实说 我付得起
Myles, honestly, I'm good for it.
‎我明早就把钱汇到你账户里
I will wire money into your account tomorrow morning.
‎这是飞马座吗
Is this Pegasus?
‎这其实是老式手机视频
Actually, it's a good, old-fashioned cell phone video
‎被一个生气的餐馆勤杂工拍下的
taken from a hella pissed-off busboy.
‎难以置信
Unbelievable.
‎这比我在飞马座上 ‎找到的东西加起来都更有价值
This is worth more than everything I've gotten from Pegasus put together.
‎你要是早告诉我能弄到这个 ‎我能省好多力气
You could've saved me a bundle if I'd known this was coming.
‎-你要拿来怎么用 ‎-我要泄露出去
-What will you do with it? -Leak it to an outlet.
‎比如给《琼斯妈妈》杂志就不错 ‎我要回去找柯克曼了
Mother Jones, I think, seems good. I gotta get back to Kirkman.
‎总统先生 有空说话吗
Mr. President. A word?
‎我想找你说话已经很久了
I've wanted to have a word with you for quite some time.
‎我只想听你道歉
The only thing I wanna hear from you is an apology.
‎我只需要你给我解释
And all I need from you is an explanation.
‎诽谤竞选策略是一回事
Smear campaign is one thing.
‎你指控我是恐怖分子就越界了
You crossed a line when you accused me of being a terrorist.
‎-我没说过 ‎-没有
-I haven't said that. -No.
‎没有 你很懦弱 ‎让你的女发言人替你说的
No, you took the chicken shit route and had your spokesgirl say it for you.
‎艾米丽罗德没有发表任何声明 ‎声称你有罪或无辜
Emily Rhodes hasn't released any statement proclaiming your guilt or innocence.
‎她只是在问大家都在问的问题
She's simply asking the questions that everyone else is.
‎这问题让我夜不能寐 你参与了吗
The question that kept me up all night. Were you?
‎你很清楚我和这没关系…
You know goddamn well I had nothing to do with it--
‎-我不清楚 ‎-胡说你了解我
-I do not know that. -Bullshit! You know me!
‎我以为我了解 ‎直到你和那个种族主义者穿一条裤子
I thought I did until you got into bed with that racist,
‎那个传播仇恨的理论家 菲尔布朗顿
hate-spewing ideologue, Phil Brunton.
‎菲尔布朗顿是个聪明的藤校生
Phil Brunton was a brilliant Ivy League kid
‎他很了解美国人民的心声
with his thumb on the pulse of the heartland.
‎我从不知道他是个疯子
I had no idea he had a screw loose.
‎你怎么回事我曾经尊敬过你
What the hell happened to you? I used to respect you.
‎你以前是个思虑周全 ‎善良慈悲的保守派
You used to be a thoughtful, compassionate Conservative.
‎这种稀有动物你最近见过多少
And how many of those unicorns have you seen lately?
‎没有 我跟随我的选民们转右了
No, sir. I shifted right when my constituents did.
‎我觉得你做了个糟糕的误算
And I think you've made a gross miscalculation.
‎你所迎合的人也许叫得最大声
The people you're pandering to might be the most vocal,
‎但他们不是你党派中的大多数
but they're not the majority of your party.
‎孩子 遗憾的是 你和时代脱节了
Son, you are sadly out of step with the times.
‎我们周二见分晓
Well, Tuesday will tell.
‎我为自己认为正确的事孤注一掷
I've gone all-in for what I think is right for the heart
‎这个国家的大多数…
and majority of this country--
‎把煽情留给你下一站的野蛮人吧
Save the saccharine for the yahoos at your next stop,
‎拜托 你可别站在那告诉我
and, please, don't stand there and tell me
‎你没有迎合极左
that you aren't flagrantly pandering to the far left.
‎-选亚伦萧做你的副总统 ‎-他是最佳候选人
-Picking Aaron Shore as your VP? -He was the best candidate.
‎你宣布竞选伙伴时
You know, when you came out with the announcement about your running mate,
‎我说：“这孩子 ‎终于学会玩这个游戏了”
I said, "That boy has learned to play the game."
‎别扯了 科尼利厄斯 这不是游戏
God damn it, Cornelius. This is not a game.
‎这当然是
Of course it is!
‎你高高在上俯视政治
You hold yourself above politics,
‎但事实是 你和我一样是个政治家
but the truth is you're every bit as much a politician as I am.
‎如果那是真的 请上帝救我
God help me if that's true.
‎我没想到你会有勇气
You know, I didn't think you'd have the balls
‎让你小姨子 或者随便你怎么称呼
to pull your sister-in-law, or whatever you call her,
‎离开竞选活动
out of your programme.
‎明智之举
Smart move.
当蒂
‎当蒂 现在我不方便
Dontae, it's not a good time.
‎别挂 你说得对
Don't hang up. You were right.
‎罗琳在莫斯阵营肯定有间谍
Lorraine definitely has a mole in Moss' campaign.
‎是莫斯数码事务的人员 他叫迈尔斯
It's Moss' digital guy. His name is Myles.
‎-当蒂 对不起 我… ‎-这比你想的还要巨大
-Dontae, I'm sorry, I-- -This is way bigger than you thought.
‎如果我没听错
If I heard what I think I just heard,
‎他们俩在搞一些严重违法的玩意
the two of them are messing with some seriously illegal shit.
‎比水门事件还要严重
Like, beyond Watergate illegal.
‎叫作飞马座
It's called Pegasus.
‎这是一款以色列间谍软件 ‎可以让你在所有者不知情的情况下
It's Israeli spy software that lets you read text messages,
‎-读到短信、追踪电话… ‎-听着 对不起…
-track calls, collect passwords... -Look, I'm sorry--
‎…收集密码 ‎并且远程打开设备录像录音
...and remotely turn on a device to record without the owner's knowledge.
‎这项技术本应只能是 ‎政府用于对付恐怖分子
This is tech that is only supposed to be available to governments to combat terror.
‎这很糟糕 艾米丽
This is bad, Emily.
‎极为糟糕
End-of-the-road bad.
‎-你在竞选办公室吗 ‎-不在
-Are you at the campaign office? -No.
‎你能去吗
Can you get there?
‎对不起 我不能
I'm sorry, I can't.
‎我们今晚去之前 ‎你要登陆罗琳的电脑
Before we get in tonight, you have to get onto Lorraine's computer.
‎看看她是不是真的有飞马座软件
See if she really has the Pegasus software.
‎我不知道她的密码
I don't know her password.
‎不是我歧视老年人
Not to be ageist,
‎但上年纪的人喜欢把密码写在手边
but people of a certain age tend to keep it written down nearby.
‎我看她从 ‎最上面抽屉里的便利贴上读过密码
I saw her read it from a Post-it in her top drawer.
‎-我不能… ‎-这不是为了我
-I can't-- -I'm not asking for me.
‎是为了柯克曼
It's for Kirkman.
‎拜托 你必须去
-Come on, you have to. -
‎-好 我会去的 ‎-谢谢
-Okay, I'll go. I'll go. -Thank you.
‎我要挂了
I gotta go.
‎我今天能站在这里
I'm only standing here today
‎都是因为我身边 ‎这位非凡的女性 伊莎贝尔帕尔多
because of this amazing woman by my side, Isabel Pardo.
柯克曼 萧
‎从最开始 她就是我坚实的后盾
She has been my rock since the very beginning of this journey.
‎谢谢你 伊莎
Thank you. Thank you, Isi.
‎我知道你们选蓝或者选红的思想 ‎已根深蒂固
Uh... I know you have it ingrained in you to vote blue or to vote red.
‎但结果呢
But where has that gotten you?
‎-你们觉得被代表了吗 ‎-没有
-Do you feel represented? - No!
‎-你们是否应该被代表是 ‎-是
-Do you deserve to be represented? Yes. - Yes!
‎那就打破循环
Then break the cycle.
‎做出不同的选择
Make a different choice.
‎选择一个独立候选人
An Independent choice.
‎创造历史
Make history.
‎让这个人成为 ‎我们的第一位拉丁裔副总统
Make this man our first Latino vice president!
‎谢谢
Thank you.
‎你可能刚刚赢下了佛罗里达
You may have just won Florida.
‎我觉得是你赢下的
I think you may have.
‎伊莎 我们做得很棒 不是吗
Isi, we're pretty good at this, aren't we?
‎你想再试试吗
You wanna give it another shot?
‎我们别太着急 好吗
Let's not get ahead of ourselves, okay?
‎-好吧 是 ‎-我要去找我爸妈了
-All right. Yeah. -I gotta go find my parents.
‎好
Okay.
‎该死
Holy hell.
‎这里是哈珀的办公室
Harper's office.
‎嘿 菲利克斯 ‎给哈珀打开《琼斯妈妈》的网站
Hey, Felix, pull up the Mother Jones website for Harper.
‎让他马上看头条故事里的视频
Have him watch the video in the lead story now.
‎（莫斯的最终解决方案）
Felix, get me POTUS.
‎菲利克斯 给我接总统
I wanted to tell you that I'm sorry. I was wrong.
‎我想告诉你我很抱歉 我错了
I should have let you introduce me.
‎我应该让你介绍我的
Easy to say now.
‎现在说说很容易
But I didn't realize how wrong I was
‎但我之前没意识到自己错得多离谱
until someone who I have absolutely no respect for
‎直到我完全不尊重的某个人
told me I was just like him.
‎告诉我 我和他一样
And he wasn't completely wrong.
‎他说的并不全错
How so?
‎为什么
What I did was a purely calculated political move.
‎我的所作所为完全是出于政治计算
It wasn't something that I thought was right.
‎而不是我认为正确的事
And I didn't get into politics to behave like a politician.
‎而我进入政坛 ‎不是为了像个政客一样行事
I'm sorry. It'll never happen again.
‎对不起 不会再有下次了
I didn't enjoy playing the gracefully suffering trans woman.
‎我不喜欢扮演一个 ‎优雅的苦难跨性别女性
I promise not to do that again.
‎我保证不会再这样做了
- -Excuse me.
‎抱歉
Yeah?
‎喂
- I'm sorry. -We're cool.
‎-对不起 ‎-我们没事了
Okay.
‎好
I'll call you right back.
‎我马上再打给你
The America that everyone in this room
‎这个房间里的各位 ‎所了解和热爱的美国正在改变
knows and loves is changing.
‎根据最新人口普查来看
According to the latest census projection,
‎到2045年 ‎这个国家的白人将成为少数
by 2045, this country will become minority white.
‎也就是说2050年前的某个时候
That means at some point before 2050,
‎白人占人口总比会小于50%
whites will account for less than 50% of the population.
‎与之相对的是
And that will be up against
‎25%西班牙裔
25% Hispanics,
‎15%黑人和5%亚洲人
15% blacks, 5% Asians
‎还有其他7%的多民族人口
and 7% your other multiracial populations.
‎如果再这样下去
If things continue down this path,
‎如果我们不能说服人们阻止这个状况
and if we fail to persuade people otherwise,
‎这些数字会让另一个政党得利
these numbers are going to favor the other party.
‎我们会落选 失去权力
We are going to be voted out of office, and we will lose our grip on power.
‎混蛋
Son of a bitch!
‎永远而彻底地失去
Completely and forever.
‎现在 我们要问自己
The question we have to ask ourselves is,
‎“这是我想居住的国家吗”
"Is that the country you want to live in?"
‎不是
No.
‎难以置信
Unbelievable.
罗琳齐默
‎你说得对
You were right.
‎-什么 ‎-关于莫斯
-About what? -Moss.
‎-你看过《琼斯妈妈》的视频了吗 ‎-没有
-Have you seen the Mother Jones video? -No.
‎怎么了
What?
莫斯的最终解决方案
‎你要怎么办
What are you gonna do?
‎没有飞马座 当蒂
There's no Pegasus, Dontae.
‎她可能不会这样标记
She probably wouldn't label it that.
‎虽然他们没成功 但毫无疑问
Even though they were unsuccessful, make no mistake,
‎我们的民主遭到了攻击
our democracy was under attack.
飞马
‎或者是他的父母
Maybe his parents.
‎考虑到他和菲尔布朗顿 ‎及加略特德特维尔的关系
With his connection to Phil Brunton and Garrett Detwiler,
‎现在又有这个极度激进的视频…
and now the release of this incredibly offensive video...
‎波塞冬
Poseidon.
‎美杜莎
Medusa.
‎听过候选人莫斯本人的陈述后
After hearing candidate Moss in his own words,
‎我被迫得出了自己的结论
I was forced to draw my own conclusions,
‎现在美国人民也要得出自己的结论了
and now it is time for the American people to do the same.
科尼利厄斯莫斯
‎该死 加略特 ‎你和菲尔对我做了什么
God damn it, Garrett!  What the fuck have you and Phil done to me?
‎你们为什么背着我做这么卑鄙的事
Why would you do this despicable thing behind my back?
‎你们到底为什么这么做
Why would you do it at all?
‎我的天啊
Oh, my God.
‎你认为莫斯总统 ‎担有国内恐怖主义的罪名吗
You believe President Moss is guilty of domestic terrorism?
‎是的
Yes, I do.
‎莫斯不知情
Moss didn't know.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177